<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>NewHSKEvents</name>
	<author>HSK Team</author>
	<url>https://github.com/skyarkhangel/Hardcore-SK</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>hsk.newhskevents</packageId>
	<description>
[English]
Adds new events for Hardcore SK modpack.
- Curious Animals: A herd of animals has taken an interest in your colonists and settled near the colony for a couple of days, curiously watching the settlers go about their lives before eventually wandering off.
- Wild Bird Attack: Flocks of aggressive birds swoop in from three sides, diving at colonists, attacking, then flying to new positions to strike again.
- Straw Fire: Someone left a piece of glass near straw matting and the sun ignited it.
- Cabin Fever Animals: Animals kept in a closed room too long suddenly go rabid and attack everything.
- Animal Snap: One of your small tame animals suddenly becomes aggressive and attacks a nearby animal.
- Crop Mineral Deficiency: If you have too few tame animals, crops die from lack of natural fertilization.

[Russian]
Добавляет новые события для модпака Hardcore SK.
- Любопытные животные: стадо животных заинтересовалось вашими колонистами и обосновалось неподалёку на пару дней, с любопытством наблюдая за жизнью поселенцев, прежде чем уйти восвояси.
- Нападение диких птиц: стаи агрессивных птиц налетают с трёх сторон, пикируют на колонистов, атакуют и перелетают на новые позиции для повторной атаки.
- Пожар на соломе: кто-то оставил рядом с соломенным покрытием что-то стеклянное — солнце подожгло солому.
- Бешенство взаперти: животные, которых долго держат в закрытом помещении, внезапно впадают в бешенство.
- Взбесившееся животное: одно из ваших мелких домашних животных внезапно стало агрессивным и напало на ближайшее животное.
- Нехватка минералов: если у вас мало домашних животных, урожай гибнет из-за нехватки естественного удобрения.
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadBefore>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
	</incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
